<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Samples on Katie Wakelin</title><link>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/</link><description>Recent content in Samples on Katie Wakelin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ballerina Bambinos: New Online Class for Toddlers</title><link>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/sample-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 14:00:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/sample-3/</guid><description>MAILING LIST EMAIL - SPECULATIVE SAMPLE
Hello John!
I hope your summer’s been fun, and that you’re surviving the chaos of back-to-school season.
We know this can be a stressful time, so we’ve put together a treat for you and your little one - that doesn’t involve yet another car trip!
Ballerina Bambinos - Online
Weekly online ballet classes for ages 2-5. Teacher: Jane Smith Starting: 15th September Time: Every Tuesday, 5pm Platform: Zoom Sign-ups are open - simply reply to this email to pre-register.</description></item><item><title>Eco-Friendly Bullet Journal</title><link>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/sample-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 14:00:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/sample-2/</guid><description>SALES PAGE - SPECULATIVE SAMPLE
The Eco-Friendly Bullet Journal is the beautiful, ethically-produced notebook you’ve been searching for. [Shop now!] Create without limits Our 160gsm paper lets you go wild with decoration. And with our wide range of colours and designs, you can choose a journal that inspires you whenever you look at it.
Organise yourself without hassle Numbered pages and a built-in index make organising your spreads easy.
Feel good every time you pick it up The vegan plant-leather cover feels luxurious in your hands, while remaining gentle on the environment.</description></item><item><title>How to Pack for a UK Summer Walking Holiday</title><link>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/sample-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 14:00:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kwakelin.github.io/samples/sample-1/</guid><description>BLOG POST - SPECULATIVE SAMPLE
So you’ve chosen your UK summer walking destination, everything’s booked, and all that’s left to do is pack! And that’s when the dread hits you. What if you forget something? What if you can’t fit everything in? What if you get halfway up a mountain and realise you did need the kitchen sink after all?
Never fear, by the power of this checklist you can pack exactly what you need, without your rucksack bursting at the seams!</description></item></channel></rss>